{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","address":"555 E Lafayette Ave","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Cleveland Simmons","licenseNumber":"078053","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/12/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":null,"riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E610000074AF3FFBA4C254C0503B2D26D32A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44591","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","inspectionDate":"2018-12-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44591","inspectionDate":"12/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"44591","inspectionDate":"12/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"44591","inspectionDate":"12/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"42400","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","inspectionDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"127","pcount":"2","pfcount":"2","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42400","inspectionDate":"6/4/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"inspectionid":"42400","inspectionDate":"6/4/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Raw animal product(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not separated from each other","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep separate."},{"inspectionid":"42400","inspectionDate":"6/4/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"inspectionid":"42400","inspectionDate":"6/4/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Hand-drying towels","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"42400","inspectionDate":"6/4/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"Without use of trapping devices Fly strips","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Utilize trapping devices to help eliminate pests."}]},{"inspectionid":"40328","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","inspectionDate":"2017-10-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"129","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40328","inspectionDate":"10/10/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in Â¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under Â§ 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in Â¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under Â§ 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"beverage dispensing nozzles","problemDescription":"Not cleaned when contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Pop Gun","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean properly when contaminated."},{"inspectionid":"40328","inspectionDate":"10/10/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"","location":"STEAMER","subLocation":"At the AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"40328","inspectionDate":"10/10/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Handwashing soap","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"40328","inspectionDate":"10/10/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Labels","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"inspectionid":"40328","inspectionDate":"10/10/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Hand-drying towels","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"38381","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","inspectionDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"129","pcount":"2","pfcount":"1","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38381","inspectionDate":"3/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"38381","inspectionDate":"3/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ÂºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ÂºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ÂºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Cooler (drawers)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"38381","inspectionDate":"3/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under Â§ 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"In large container","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the COOLING METHODS","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize long, shallow pans."},{"inspectionid":"38381","inspectionDate":"3/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"38381","inspectionDate":"3/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Cooler (drawers)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"38381","inspectionDate":"3/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\r\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ÂºF to 70ÂºF; and (P) \r\n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ÂºF to 41ÂºF or less (P)\r\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\r\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ÂºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ÂºF or less. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 70 degrees f to 41 degrees F for more than 4 hours","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the COOLING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"36673","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","inspectionDate":"2016-10-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"130","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36673","inspectionDate":"10/4/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ÂºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ÂºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ÂºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"36673","inspectionDate":"10/4/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70Â° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41Â° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in water","subProblem":"","location":"PREP SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36673","inspectionDate":"10/4/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4460","name":"Greektown Casino - Prism","violationCode":"3-203.12","violationDescription":"SHELLSTOCK tags shall remain attached to the container in which the shellstock are received until the container is empty and tags shall be retained for 90 days after the container is empty.  Retained tags shall be kept in chronological order and correlated to the date when shellstock are harvested. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Shellstock","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Identification","subProblem":"Tag(s) not retained for 90 days","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Retain on file."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4460"}}